A feminist's journey into the Men's Rights Movement
The Red Pill is a documentary film directed by Cassie Jaye.
When a feminist filmmaker sets out to document the mysterious and polarizing world of
the Men’s Rights Movement, she begins to question her own beliefs.
Chronicling Cassie Jaye’s journey exploring an alternate
perspective on gender equality, power and privilege.
Self, played by Cassie Jaye.
Self, played by Alison Tieman.
Self, played by Attila Vinczer.
Self, played by Barbara Smith.
Self, played by Ben Evans.
Self, played by Brian de Matos.
The Red Pill is a 2016 American documentary film directed by Cassie Jaye.
The film explores the men's rights movement, as Jaye spends a year
filming the leaders and followers within the movement.
It premiered on October 7, 2016 in New York City, followed by
several other one-time screenings internationally.
It was released on DVD and Blu-ray in 2017 by Gravitas Ventures.
The film explores themes of politics, feminism,
interview, based on true story, equality.